[English subtitles are available]
[Song of the Moon]
[Episode 04]
Senior, you're hurt.
It must hurt.
Have a candy.
You won't feel so sad after.
After I have learned my skills,
I'll protect you,
just like Master protected us.
I won't let you get hurt again.
Junior, I'll wait for you to grow up.
Senior.
Watch out!
Senior, why are you here?
I heard you were injured.
I came right away.
I asked someone to distract Wang Jian,
and came to see you secretly.
Take the medicine.
I made it specially for you.
Sister,
I'm not a kid.
I can do it myself.
Senior.
Liu Shao didn't make any trouble
in the past few days, did she?
No.
If anything happens,
I'm here.
Besides,
you still care about her
when you're sick yourself.
Actually,
it's not Liu Shao's fault.
She didn't mean it.
I don't blame her.
I just hope
you can get better soon.
Do you remember?
In order to practice magic,
we've been injured constantly since we were young.
We've been supporting each other
all the way here.
Master and Senior
are the most important people to me.
I'll do my best to protect you.
I won't let anyone hurt you.
Take the medicine.
The Moon Washing Stone won't be too far from the Moon Washing Pond.
Try to infer from the prayers
and go again on a full moon night.
It won't be hard to find.
The next full moon night is just around the corner.
I wonder if Wang Jian has sent my message.
Little girl.
Lu Li.
I've been looking for you. You're here.
Are you feeling better?
Are you worried about me?
With the Lord healing me,
this injury
is nothing.
Just wait.
I'll recover soon.
Let's make a deal.
We will
practice hunting demons together.
I will wait for you to come with me.
Okay.
Remember,
this trip to the Moon Washing Pond
is different from before.
On a full moon night,
demons appear frequently.
Even Ao Hen may be alarmed.
If you are in danger,
I
may not be able to save you.
Liu Shao.
What are you thinking about?
Nothing.
Actually,
I have something to tell you.
But when I see you,
I don't know what to say.
Oh.
You came to talk to me.
You don't know how to say it after meeting me.
This is beyond my duty.
It's not easy to set the price.
Lu Li.
You...
Come.
Here.
Take it.
What is this?
This is a recording stone.
It can store what you want to say.
Of course,
it can also record what others said.
Is it that magical?
Yes.
In this case,
you don't have to wait for me for so long.
Then put it here.
I'll record messages for you later.
Okay.
It's getting late.
You should go back and rest.
Okay.
He gave me this.
Does he have a lot
to tell me too?
♫I said I miss you because of your name♫
♫I'll spend the rest of my life with you♫
♫I can't tell dreams apart♫
♫Let love continue after flowers bloom♫
♫I said I miss you, don't doubt me♫
♫You left traces in my life♫
♫I want to be with you♫
Lu Li.
♫Spring comes and winter goes. Let love continue♫
Wait for me.
♫I think the world can't hear♫
♫The four seasons have been circulating for a thousand years♫
♫You whispered forever to me♫
When a liar doesn't lie,
he's quite cute.
You must get better soon.
[Wu]
The moon is bright.
The water is surging.
According to the prayers,
[Wu]
if I walk along the water
on a full moon night.
I should be able to find the Moon Washing Stone.
There is no Moon Washing Stone.
Aren't these ordinary stones?
The beautiful stone is like jade.
It shines brightly
like it has been washed by moonlight.
This must be the Moon Washing Stone.
It can't be wrong.
Found it!
Where is the herb?
When you find the Moon Washing Stone,
irrigate it with blood.
The King Herb
will grow out of it.
Brother, how do you feel?
Although Wu Yang Duke has recuperated your body,
but your vitality is badly damaged.
You need to nourish it.
It's okay.
I have the resilience of a wild dog.
I've been fine for a while.
Your soup is good.
You're quite filial.
Have more.
By the way,
when did Liu Shao say she was going to hunt demons?
Should I prepare now?
You still care about her at this point?
You still say you have no feelings for her?
Man.
You...
You don't understand.
I do things for her for money.
Besides,
I'm working with injuries.
If she doesn't give me 3,000 or 5,000 taels,
it'll be inappropriate, right?
Yes.
You're right.
But you can't make the money.
Maybe before you recover,
she already got the demons.
That's not right.
Every time I have soup,
you have more than me.
You didn't even touch it this time.
Something is wrong with you.
Brother, don't blame me.
It was all Liu Shao's idea.
She promised the Lord
to find the King Herb in the Moon Washing Pond.
That's why he used up his vitality to save you.
Liu Shao didn't want you to worry,
so she didn't allow me to tell you.
You're being ridiculous.
Brother.
Brother, I gave her all the spells.
Wait for me.
I'll get even with you.
No, brother.
[Wu]
It turned out that
this King Herb was so easy to get.
I thought
it would be very difficult.
That's because God of the Moonlight and God of the Sun
acknowledged the power in your blood.
The King Herb nurtured by their residual spiritual power
will naturally accept you.
Who are you?
Come out!
I'm telling you. Don't scare me again.
Ao Hen.
I didn't expect
other than you,
I can get another bonus.
I'll take
both of you.
Is the lantern from the Mansion of Wu Yang Duke?
This lantern
can only scare the little Aquatic Demons.
How dare you threaten me with it?
In your dreams!
Invisible Amulet!
Oh no!
You think you can escape
with just a few amulets?
Demon King in White.
Ao Hen.
It's time to settle the score
between you and my clan.
Settle the score?
How dare you meddle in my business?
What if I insist?
Demon King in White,
I'll remember this.
You're the Demon King in White?
No.
There's no Demon King who's hard to track down.
I just pretended to be the Demon King in White
to scare her away.
You're amazing.
But I still have to thank you.
I don't help others
for free.
Of course.
How much do you want? I'll give it to you.
Where is my King Herb?
This is the reward I want.
Sorry.
My brother needs the King Herb to save his life.
I'll make it up to you in the future.
But I must make you forget me first.
Where is the King Herb?
No.
That man in white...
In white...
What does he look like?
Why can't I remember anything?
Hello?
Is anyone there?
That herb is very important to me.
If I can't bring it back,
I'll break my promise to Wu Yang Duke.
The human world will be in big trouble.
What should I do?
Hello?
Is anyone there?
Where are you? Give me back the herb!
[Palace of Aquatic Demons]
[Wu]
Liu Shao.
You must not get hurt.
I finally found you.
Don't do this again.
Acting alone without me.
What's wrong?
I'm not hurt.
But Ao Hen came after me.
The King Herb.
The King Herb is gone too.
Isn't that dangerous?
Are you really okay?
I'm really fine.
But the herb is gone.
Then I have nothing to hand over to the Lord.
It will be fine.
You lost the herb. We can think of another way.
It's all my fault.
You too.
Why did you come to this dangerous place
without telling me?
If something really happened,
how could I be at ease?
You're injured. I'm worried about you.
I hope you can rest well.
Besides,
whenever I was in trouble,
didn't you also risk your life to help me?
I can't always let you stand in front of me.
[Wu]
What a silly girl.
From now on,
I will always be with you.
[King Fu, General of Water of Aquatic Demons]
Fu.
You barely recovered.
Now is not the time to settle the score with Ao Hen.
But at least,
I have to save the rest of my people.
You haven't fully recovered yet.
Don't go out for a while.
Stay here and rest.
I'm doing it for my clan. Why are you stopping me?
They are your clan,
but also my people.
I am the Demon King.
I know what to do.
Take care of yourself.
Don't worry about the clan.
I'll find a way.
Demon King.
[Yu Yu Hall]
I've told you
how much trouble the loss of the King Herb would
bring to the human world.
Bai Feng.
Didn't I ask you to check
the demons next to the Moon Washing Pond?
My Lord,
I did check them one by one.
But I didn't find Ao Hen or her subordinates.
Aquatic Demons frequent the Moon Washing Pond.
But they always keep their promises.
[Wu]
When they see the lanterns from the Mansion of Wu Yang Duke,
they would back off.
They wouldn't make things difficult for Junior Liu Shao.
The one who took my King Herb
was in white.
He was very skilled in martial arts.
Could it be
the Demon King in White?
That's impossible.
The Demon King in White is a modest and scrupulous gentleman.
How could he be hostile to the Mansion of Wu Yang Duke?
I think
with Liu Shao's cultivation,
it's a miracle that
she returned safely.
Ao Hen the great demon
and the Demon King in White,
these big shots of the demonic world
both let you go.
I wonder what Liu Shao
promised them?
Otherwise, how could you escape
from such a powerful demon like Ao Hen?
My Lord,
I think
Junior Liu Shao is very talented.
If she uses the heaven and earth treasures to strengthen her spiritual power,
she will be able to cultivate to become a master,
she will naturally be treated differently by the great demons.
Treated differently?
Unless she betrayed the human race
and became a demon.
Liu Shao is a demon.
Maybe she has really become a demon.
No wonder she's so powerful.
It's a shame the Lord trusted her so much.
Xi died without any clear reason
after offending her.
Senior,
if I were a demon,
how could I enter the Mansion of Wu Yang Duke?
If you don't believe me,
I'll leave the Mansion of Wu Yang Duke.
Liu Shao.
What?
You took the King Herb,
and now you want to walk away?
Of course not.
Liu Shao meant that
she wants to go out and find the King Herb.
She wants to find the King Herb?
My Lord,
if I get the King Herb back,
can it prove Liu Shao's innocence?
Yes.
OK.
Please give me some time.
I will find the King Herb for you.
Lu Li.
The King Herb
only grows one plant in a hundred years.
Can you do it?
I can.
If I can't,
I'm willing to accept any punishment.
Please
give us a chance.
Brother,
can you really get the King Herb again?
The King Herb grows for a hundred years.
There is only one in the world.
How could I get it so easily?
I'm not an immortal.
So you did it to buy time.
Why are you so down?
We still have time.
Don't worry.
I'm here.
It's okay.
Yeah.
We're here for you.
Liu Shao.
I won't let anything happen to you.
Do you understand?
Then think about it carefully again.
That fake Demon King whose face you didn't see clearly,
he's in white,
and he can turn water into ice.
Is there anything else special?
There's a pendant on his flute. It's pretty.
What does it look like?
Like this.
Every flute looks like this.
No, no, no.
It's different.
Here.
There is a flower, very special.
I've never seen it before.
Draw it for me.
Okay.
Like this.
Forget it.
You describe. I'll draw it.
I draw.
Watch carefully.
This is eichhornia crassipes.
These are the patterns of the royalty of Aquatic Demons.
The only one who can control all spirits in the Three Realms
with the melody of a flute is the Demon King.
Good Heavens.
He's really the Demon King in White.
He's not an imposter.
This time, I'll tear Ao Hen into pieces.
Aquatic Demons have been cursed for generations.
We live by water.
If we leave the water, we will die.
You just recovered.
Why are you going to find Ao Hen again?
She killed my clan for the demon energy.
How can I put up with it?
Brother,
why not try to overthrow the Four Seasons Monument,
eliminate Ao Hen,
unify the demonic realm,
and welcome the God of the Moonlight back.
Let him lift the curse for us.
But Fu,
don't you know
what the Supreme God under the monument did?
Can you guarantee that he won't cause trouble to the Three Realms again?
Do you still hope
to find the inheritor of Immortal Ze Shui
to lift the curse?
I have a clue about this.
The dignified Demons
has to rely on a woman to save.
No wonder even the little demons under Ao Hen
disregarded Aquatic Demons.
I have only one creed.
If you humiliate my clan,
I'll cut you into pieces.
What?
Your Majesty are going to the Mansion of Wu Yang Duke with that girl?
That's right.
She's not afraid of the sound of my Melody Flute.
It's most likely that
she's the reincarnation of Immortal Ze Shui.
If that girl
is really the inheritor of Immortal Ze Shui,
we will have a chance
to save Aquatic Demons.
When do you plan to leave?
A few days ago,
I made a fish demon double
to follow her.
But it can't last for long.
I need to go there soon.
Okay.
I'll arrange it now.
It must be here.
Regarding the King Herb,
I must repay this girl in the future.
But now for Aquatic Demons,
I have to confirm if she's the person I'm looking for.
I need a drop of her blood.
Demon King.
Who is it?
Oh no.
We can't stay here for long.
Such a powerful spell
must be the trick of Lu Sheng, the half demon.
You must be anxious.
I'll let you out now.
Go.
Find someone you should deal with.
Lu Li.
Since you want to climb above me so badly,
enjoy
the gift I gave you.
Lu Li.
I know
you've been running around for me.
Although you have a sharp tongue,
but
when they suspected me,
you trusted me and helped me.
Knowing that you're good to me,
I'm happy.
I'm very happy.
Lu Li.
When I was young,
I wanted to learn skills
to see mountains, rivers, the sun and the moon,
and the stars of the four seas.
That's what I want now too.
But
I hope I can have someone to accompany me
to go through the clouds and the sea
to experience the magnificent life.
I hope
that person is you.
Will you?
I hope
that person is you.
-Will you? -What am I talking about?
How do I get rid of this?
Hello?
Who?
It's me.
How long have you been here?
Not long.
I just came here.
Yes.
I've found clues about the King Herb.
You don't need to worry.
Tomorrow is the first time we go out for demon hunting.
You need to stay alert.
Go back and rest early.
You too.
I'm leaving.
Be careful this time.
I...
Although I'm smart and powerful,
and the reincarnation of the lucky child,
it's my first time hunting demons. I'm inexperienced.
Brother, you...
Are you so confident
to let me charge forward?
That day,
who lied to me?
Brother!
Brother, I was wrong.
You just want me to be the bait, right?
Then I'll go.
I always do this.
Watch out!
Demon!
Don't come to me.
I'm not tasty at all.
Xue.
Be careful.
Liu Shao.
Are you okay?
Be careful.
Xue.
-Xue! -Xue, wake up.
Liu Shao.
Where is Wang Jian?
Forgive me, Your Majesty.
I never did evil before.
I was captured recently
and has been sealed.
Until two days ago,
he released me.
I was driven by the demon controling seal,
so I attacked humans.
Your Majesty, please spare my life.
Thank you, Your Majesty. Thank you, Your Majesty.
The spell in your body has been removed.
I'll cut off your demon power for 30 years.
You may leave.
Yes.
Wang Jian.
Who are you?
Tell me your name.
Demon King in White?
Why is he here?
Miss Liu Shao.
My name is Kho.
I'm your demon.
My demon? Kho?